他们来了  他们就在门外
They're here. They're out front.
-几个人  -四个
- How many? - Four.
尼尔森・布雷  和另外三个人
Nelson Brey, three others.
-你拿了他的牙刷吗  -拿了
- Did you get his toothbrush? - Got it.
你的行李呢  要不这样吧
What about your stuff? Oh, you know what?
我们让他们开到你的住处停一下
We'll talk to them about stopping at your place.
斯凯勒  斯凯勒
Skyler-- Skyler...
-怎么了  -我不走
- What? - I'm not going.
什么
What?
我不去汉克和玛丽那里
I'm not going to Hank and Marie's
我哪儿也不去
I'm not going anywhere.
可你说过我们处境危险
But you said we're in danger.
是的  没错
Yes, that's true.
-那是因为我  -现在这不重要
- Because of me. - It doesn't matter now.
重要的是
All that matters is--
重要的是你们其余人的安全
All that matters is that the rest of you are safe,
所以我才不能跟你走
and that's why I'm not going with you.
我才是他们要抓的人
I'm the real target.
可是待在汉克家  我们都会没事的
But we'll all be safer at Hank's.
不不不
That's-- No, no, no.
如果我在那儿  就没有人会没事
No one will be safe at Hank's if I'm there.
沃特  他可是毒品管制局的人
Walt, it's DEA.
斯凯勒  你不了解这些人
Skyler, you don't know these people.
-可我  -不  斯凯勒  求你了
- I-  - No, Skyler, please,
相信我
trust me.
只能如此
This is how it has to be.
门外那些探员
Walt, those agents outside--
他们可不会扔下你不管
they're not going to just leave you here!
这才叫做保护性监禁
It's called protective custody.
他们只知道汉克一人
All they know is that Hank is the only person
目前有危险
that's in danger.
他们捎上我们  只是处于对玛丽的尊重
They're including us only as a courtesy to Marie,
让她宽心
just to keep her happy.
可我该怎么对玛丽  儿子
How am I supposed to explain that to Marie--
和汉克  解释这件事
or Junior or Hank, for that matter?
我不知道  但你必须解释
I don't know, but you'll do it.
你会想出法子的
You'll figure it out.
汉克知道玛丽会反应过激
Hank knows that Marie will be overreacting.
她肯定会焦躁不安
Except she's not.
我会去跟汉克说
I'll talk to Hank.
剩下所有人都交给你解释了
You just back me up with everyone else.
你真的希望我去说
You really expect me to say
"好了  沃尔特就待在那儿了..."
"Okay, Walt, sure, just stay here and..."
不  肯定还有别的办法
No, there's got to be another way.
没有了
There isn't.
曾经有过
There was,
但现在没有了
but now there isn't.
沃特
Walt,
你要多久才会安全
how long till you're safe,
才能脱身
till you can work this out?
斯凯勒
Oh, Skyler...
-斯凯勒  -不要
- Skyler-  - No.
这一年来  我备受死亡的威胁
I have lived under the threat of death for a year now,
因为它
and because of that,
我已经做出了选择
I've made choices.
-沃尔特  -听我说
- Walt-  - Listen to me.
我一个人该承担这些选择
I alone should suffer the consequences
造成的后果  而不连累其他人
of those choices, no one else.
而这些后果
And those consequences--
就要来了
they're coming.
该来的总会来的
No more prolonging the inevitable.
系上背带  对  就从安全带扣里穿过去
Feed that belt-- yep, right through those seatbelt holders
非常感谢  汉克
Thank you so much. Hank,
洗车场还要营业
I've got a car wash to run.
我是说  你不会真觉得
I mean, you don't honestly believe
我会有危险吧  就凭我
that I'm in danger, do you? Me?
老天
Oh, Jesus,
弄得这么大张旗鼓的
everything's going to go over like a lead balloon.
玛丽一定会杀了我
It'll be Marie who kills me.
好了  就告诉你一声
All right, well, just know
我会尽快赶到那里
that I'll get there as soon as I can,
也通知史蒂芬・戈麦斯一声
and let Steve Gomez know.
我跟他那几个人说了  注意安全
I told some of his guys, and just stay safe.
拜托
Oh, please.
不至于那么夸张
Whole thing's just a giant jerk-off.
是啊是啊  但你还是小心为好
Yeah, yeah, but keep your head down anyway, all right?
好吧
All right.
兄弟  保重
All right, buddy, take care.
我知道
I know.
好了  我的宝贝  我们没事了
Okay, my love. We're okay.
好了  宝宝  没关系
Okay, baby. Honey, It's okay.
好了
Okay...
第四季 第十二集
S04E12: End Times
他为了这家愚蠢的洗车场连命都不要了
He's going to risk his life over a stupid car wash?
他明不明白
Does he even understand
汉克舅舅出的是什么事
what's going on with Uncle Hank?
他能来的时候自然会来
He'll come when he's able.
真可悲
That's pathetic.
你到底有没有努力说服他
How hard did you even try, or did you?
对你妈客气点
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey. Lay off your mom.
汉克  如果你和史蒂芬能让他来
Well, you know, Hank, we wouldn't even be arguing about this
我们就不必在这儿吵了
if you and Steve would just make him come.
你们为何不硬抓他上车
Why didn't your people put him in the car?
因为这里不是纳粹德国  好吗
Uh, because it's not Nazi German, all right?
什么纳粹德国啊
Oh, pl-- you-- Nazi Germany.
要是我每听到这话就能得到一块钱的话
If I had a dollar for every time
早就发了
I heard that.
知道吗  我要去给他打电话
You know what? I'm going to call him.
他必须立刻躲到这里来
He's going to get his behind here immediately.
没得商量
End of story.
谢谢你  至少还有人在听我说话
Thank you. At least somebody is listening to me.
因为我们都很危险
Because we are all in danger here.
我们没有都很危险
We are not all in danger.
你能别这么说吗
Will you stop saying that?
这就是自找麻烦
That is asking for trouble.
接电话  沃尔特
Oh, come on, Walt.
他不接电话
He's not picking up.
我们能都放轻松一点吗
Look, could we just take this down a notch?
行吗  各位
Okay, everybody?
斯凯  你们在这儿想待多久都行
Sky, you guys can stay here as long as you like, okay?
我们有足够的房间
We've got plenty of room.
但我不必担心沃尔特或我们任何人的安全
But I wouldn't worry about any danger to Walt or any of us.
好吗
Okay?
这整件事只是烟幕弹
This whole thing's just a damn smoke screen.
你什么意思  烟幕弹
How do you mean a-- a smoke screen?
给我写什么匿名恐吓
An anonymous threat against me?
我都坐上轮椅了  我甚至不在岗位上
I'm stuck in a wheelchair. I'm not even on the job.
错了  是有人不满意我最近的业余活动
No, someone doesn't like the way I've been spending my free time.
什么活动  买矿石吗
What, minerals?
你不觉得太巧了吗
Timing seem a bit odd to you, huh?
你看  我才刚开始查那个谁
I mean, I start looking into, you know...
福林  突然之间就被禁足了
Fring, and all of a sudden I'm under lockdown for my...
等一下  你说谁
Wait a minute. Whoa, whoa, whoa. What?
古斯・福林
Gus Fring?
炸鸡店老板
From the chicken restaurant?
汉克  你说的是什么呀
Hank, what are you talking about?
个人观点
Just one man's humble opinion.
仅此而已
That's all,
不过我认为洛博罗炸鸡馆
but I think Los Pollos Hermanos
是西南最大冰毒贩的幌子
is a front for the biggest meth distributor in the Southwest
我的上帝  史蒂芬
Oh, my God. Steve...
我的上帝  你们...有在查这件事吗
Oh, my God. Are you-- Are you even looking into this?
我们不会放过任何线索
We're looking into everything,
但是我们的行动必须基于事实而非猜测
but we work on fact, not conjecture,
事实就是  当初袭击你的王八蛋
and the fact is that the scumbags that hit you first
来自墨西哥贩毒集团
were Mexican cartel,
不是什么德资跨国集团
not some German multinational whatever,
更不是肯德基上校[指福林]
and definitely not Colonel Sanders.
哪怕我们有一丁点儿的证据
Now, if we even had a shred of proof--
给你薪水不就是让你找证据的吗
Isn't that what you get paid to go get?
记得我跟你讲过的洗衣店吧
Remember that laundry I told you about?
是我就从那边开查
I'd start there.
想想啊  兄弟
Come on, man.
完美的冰毒实验室选址
It's a perfect spot for a meth superlab.
我的上帝
Oh, my God.
万一我猜对了呢
What if I'm right?
即便你猜对了
Even if you were right--
虽然那不可能
and you ain't--
但是就算你猜对了  我也绝对没有可能
but if you were, there's no way in hell
拿到法官批准的搜查令
a judge is going to give me a search warrant--
要搜查令干什么
Search warrant?
直接上门访谈的好传统被丢弃了吗
What happened to good, old-fashioned knock and talk?
哦对  我忘了
Oh, that's right. I forgot.
那从来不是你长项  是不是
You were never very good at those, were you?
-要帮忙吗  -这样的  先生
- Can I help you? - Yes, sir.
我和我兄弟们能不能在你这查一下
My friend and I... we wondered if we could take a look around.
为什么
Why?
-不好意思  你叫什么  -丹尼斯
- Sorry, what's your name? - Dennis.
丹尼斯  我是史蒂芬・戈麦斯
Dennis. Hey, I'm Steve Gomez.
毒品管制局  禁毒署的
I'm with the DEA, Drug Enforcement.
怎么了  有什么问题吗
What, is there-- there a problem?
没问题  没你的事
Not for you. No, no problem.
我们只是想检查一下
We're just wondering if we could take a look around.
我...
I, uh--
能给你讲个事吗
Can I tell you a story?
-行啊  -我抓到一个厨师
- Yeah. - I bust this chef.
他自称是厨师
Well, he says he's a chef,
可是在餐厅打工
but just because you work at a restaurant
一个汉堡卖到14块
that charges $14 for a burger,
不能算是厨师
that don't make you a chef.
顶多是个有手艺的做汉堡的
That makes you a glorified burger flipper,
至少我是这么认为
at least in my book.
总之吧
Anyway,
我们抓了这个携带海洛因的厨师
so we bust this chef-- heroin possession.
他就狡辩  "你们在我工装兜里
He says, "Well, just because you found heroin
找到海洛因也不能证明就是我的
"In my chef whites doesn't make it mine.
说不准是洗工装的洗衣房放进去的呢"
Maybe it came from the place that launders my chef whites"
就是你家了
this place.
老哥  我们这儿可没有那东西
Oh, come on, man. I don't want to do this stuff with you.
我懂我懂
I-I know, I know.
不用你说  我也清楚
You don't have to say it. I'll say it for you.
他就是满嘴胡编乱扯
His story is a big load of steaming horse shit.
你这儿能找到海洛因
I mean, we're going to find heroin here
拉登早都抓住了
like we're going to find Jimmy Hoffa. Right?
问题是  这厨子的老爹
The thing is, is that the chef's daddy
是联邦参议员
is a United States Senator.
我不告诉你是哪个
I'm not going to tell you which one,
你八成也能猜出来  是吧
but you probably know who he is, right?
所以现在我的浪费时间
So now I've got to waste my time
核实这个做汉堡的编的瞎话
checking out this burger flipper's story,
如果我不查  他老子就会给我小鞋穿
and if I don't, his old man's going to jam me up,
给我的助手  我们整个组的人穿
my ASAC, my whole entire office.
政客难缠啊
Politics, huh?
你意下如何
So what do you think?
是这么回事
Listen, you know what?
我得跟老板请示  他出城去了
I have to check with my boss, and he's out of town,
我也不能保证很快联系到他
and I can't promise I'll reach him anytime soon either, you know?
那就只好这么办了
Well, yeah, that's probably the way to go,
我得申请搜查令
so I'll have to go get a warrant,
一切按部就班来
and we'll do it official,
那样的话你们今天就得停业
but you're probably going to have to close down for the day.
什么  为什么
What-- why?
二十个探员四处查看
Twenty agents poking around?
想想吧  只我们俩来岂不是少了很多麻烦
Come on, it'll be less trouble if it was just us two,
你决定
but your call.
只有你们两个
Just the two of you?
你们会很快的是吧
You'll make it quick, right?
丹尼斯  我们来去如风
Dennis, we'll be like the wind.
那成
O-Okay.
-你跟他说  -行啦
- Could you tell him? Okay.
成啦
Okay.
丹尼斯  能不能帮忙把工人请出去
Oh, and, Dennis, can you clear out some of your people for us?
免得狗嗅错了
Confuses the dog's nose.
需要关机安静多久
So how long we gotta be quiet down her?
之后会怎么样
Then what happens after this,
假如他们没发现地下室  把我们都逮走的话
provided they don't find their way in here and bust our asses?
我是不是就  这辈子都
I'm gonna be, like, stuck down here in a laundry hamper
困在洗衣房地下了
for the rest of eternity?
我这话你记住
No, I'm going on record.
真是操蛋
This-- This blows.
喂
Hello.
找你
For you.
是我
Yeah?
你知不知道地面上发生了什么事
Do you know what's happening upstairs?
我清楚得很
I have a pretty good idea.
这都是拜你的前搭档所赐
This is all the result of your former partner.
你现在懂了吗
Do you understand now?
为什么不能这样下去
Do you see why this can't continue?
我都明白
You know, I get it.
他是个混账王八蛋
The guy's a complete and total dick,
可我不能
but I can't--
我说过的话没变
I'm not signing off.
懂吗
Okay?
我之前说过了
Like I said,
如果怀特老师
if something final
有个三长两短
happens to Mr. White,
你我就有麻烦了
we are going to have a problem.
你打算怎么做
So what are you going to do?
我会做出适当的回应
There will be an appropriate response.
适当  是什么意思
Appropriate? What does that mean?
喂
Hello?
他们走了
They're gone.
可以开工了
We're good.
请在嘀声后  留下你的姓名
At the tone, please state your name,
电话号码  和打来的原因
number, and the reason for your call.
谢谢合作
Thank you.
你有六条新留言
You have six new messages.
孩子  是我  古德曼
Hey, kid, it's me, Goodman.
速度给我回电
Give me a call, would you?
喂  急需和你谈谈
Hey, need to hear from you. All right?
我想我已经说的很清楚了
Hope I made myself clear about that.
尽快给我回电
Call me as soon as you can.
平克曼  快给我过来  速度
Pinkman, get over here. Stat, pronto.
别打电话  给我直接过来
Don't call. Just get over here.
你能不能  求你了
Would you just...? Please.
我不知道是不是你听不懂我的话
I don't know if I'm speaking English here--
怎么了  他在等我
What's up? He's waiting for me, yo.
稍等  稍等
Hold up, hold up.
你干什么  老兄
The hell, man?
别碰我
Get off of me!
古德曼  快给我出来
Hey, Goodman! Get out here!
别碰我
Get-- Hey!
你个变态别碰我
Yo, get your goon off me.
不是他  白痴  放下  坐下
Not him, moron. Drop. Leave it. Go lie down.
对不起  这几天不得不得小心点
Sorry, you can't be too careful these days.
快进来  把门锁上  弗里斯基
Come on, come on. Lock the door, Frisky.
我的天哪
Jesus.
去休息一下吧  H.T  去吧
Take a break, H.T. Let's go.
别再这么叫我
You're going to stop calling me that,
不然我就用你的领带绞死你
or I'm going to hang you by your tie.
好  好  别再客户面前卖弄了
Yeah, yeah, stop showing off for the client.
亲爱的小咪咪  是说你很讨人喜爱
Honey Tits. I say it's endearing.
什么事这么重要
So what's so important?
他们来了
Well, they're here--
没时间了  孩子
the end times, kid.
没时间了
End times.
什么意思
What's that mean?
为什么你把我拉来这
And why the hell you drag me down here for?
你想要你的钱不是吗
You want your money, don't you?
我想你应该想
I assume that you do.
什么  这有什么好急的
What, that couldn't wait?
你听说过人间蒸发这个词吗  孩子
You ever hear the expression "A fart in the wind," Kid?
我在一个小时内就会这样了
Well, inside of an hour, that's going to be me, okay?
我要跑路了  我要离开这里
I'm hitting the road. I'm gone. I'm out of here.
你说什么  真的走了
What, for, like, good?
因为必须如此
For as long as it takes.
你懂我的意思的话  我不想把话说得太明
I don't like my heat so hot, if you catch my drift.
我不懂你到底在说什么
I'm not catching, like, anything you're saying,
你到底怎么了
and what the hell is your problem?
你没和你搭档说过话吧
You haven't talked to your partner, have you?
从昨晚开始就没有
No, not since last night.
今天他都没来工作
Today he didn't show up to work,
毒品管制局还正好来突击搜查
and the DEA just happened to, like, raid us.
没错  有点太巧了  对吧
Yeah, some coincidence, huh?
这我倒是不清楚
Yeah, I don't know about that.
我只知道  他告诉我
All I know is when he tells me
你们的雇主把他带到沙漠里
that your employer took him out in the desert
然后威胁要灭他全家
and threatened to murder his entire family,
我突然想到
I sit up and take notice
因为毕竟我不是他的家人  我会被怎么样
because, hey, after all, what am I if not family?
你在说什么
What are you-- What are you talking about?
什么时候的事情
When did that happen?
我不知道  当我没说
I don't know. Forget it.
他有点夸张了  他经常这样
He-- He exaggerates, right? He does that.
听着  帮我个忙
Hey, listen, do me a favor.
能在福林面前说说我好话吗
Would you put in a good word for me with Fring?
看在我们这么久交情上
I mean, just for old time's sake.
这些话我真说不出口
I can't afford to butter the wrong bread here.
明白了吧
Yeah.
没有发现  是吗
Nothing, huh?
非常干净
Clean as a whistle,
他也这么说
so he says.
这里是沃尔特・怀特
You have reached Walter White.
请在嘀声后  留下你的姓名
At the tone, please state your name,
电话号码  和打来的原因
number, and the reason for your call.
谢谢合作
Thank you.
还是我
It's me again.
真希望你能接电话
I really wish you'd pick up.
天呐  我只是
God, I just--
给我回个电话  好吗
Call me back, okay?
给我回个电话  求你了
Just-- Just call me back, please.
很抱歉  我能在这里呆一会吗
Hi, I'm sorry. Is it okay if I come out here for a few minutes?
当然  别出去就行
Yeah, sure, just stay up here, if you would.
打扰了  我想问
Excuse me, I wonder
你有烟么
if you have a-- an extra cigarette?
我现在想抽支烟
I sure could use a smoke right about now.
当然
Sure.
谢谢
Thank you.
多谢
Thanks.
什么事
Hey, what's up?
什么
What?
他怎么了
What's wrong with him?
哪家医院
What hospital?
安德莉亚
Andrea.
杰西
Jesse.
-布洛克在哪  -他们把他带进去了
- Where's Brock? - They've got him inside.
奶奶正陪着他
Grandma's with him.
他们让我填这些单子
They got me filling out all this paperwork--
他现在怎么样了  告诉我发生了什么
How's he doing? Tell me what's going on?
医生们说  他们也不知道这是什么
The doctors-- they don't know what it is exactly.
他就像得了流感一样
It's like-- It's like he's got the flu,
可他的情况却越来越糟
but-- but he just keeps getting worse.
杰西  我不明白
Jess, I don't understand.
他早上还好好的
He was fine this morning.
他本来好好的
He was fine.
哪个是安德莉亚・坎蒂略的家人
Andrea Cantillo?
我是
Right here.
坎蒂略夫人  我们要
Ms. Cantillo, we're going to go ahead
将你的儿子送往儿科重症监护病房
and admit your son to the pediatric ICU.
-把这些带上  -好的
- You can bring that with you. - Okay.
你是孩子的父亲吗
So you're the boy's father?
-不是  -好吧  对不起
- No. - Okay, I'm sorry.
我们最多只能接受两名访客  请谅解
It's just we try to keep it to two visitors maximum, so-- okay?
没关系  你快去  我就在外面
No, go, go. I'll be out here if you need me.
快去
Go, go ahead.
不要啊
No, no.
No.
不要啊
No...No...No...
No... no...
不要啊
Come on.
No!
安德莉亚
Andrea!
Andr--
喂  别大喊大叫
Hey, hey, hey, no yelling.
-安德莉亚  我要和他  -我们不能再让你进去了
- Andrea-- I need-- - We can't have you back here.
我要和她谈谈  我要和她谈谈
No, I need to talk to her. All right? I need to talk to her.
你们两个  出去谈
You two, just take this outside.
请你们
Would you please--
布洛克还在里面奄奄一息呢
Brock is sick in here.
跟我来
Come here-- Here.
杰西
Jesse...
杰西  干什么
Jesse, what is it?
杰西  我不能走
Jesse, I can't go.
布洛克还留在这里
Brock stays in here.
好的  那
Okay. What--
我  我想布洛克
I'm-- I'm thinking Brock
可能是被下毒了  明白吗
may have been poisoned. Okay?
什么
What?
这个东西  这个东西叫蓖麻毒素
There's this stuff, this stuff called ricin.
听起来像米饭的发音
It sounds like "Rice."
你得去告诉医生
You need to tell the doctors about it.
你为什么这么说  你怎么知道
Why would you say that? How do you know?
那不重要  只要告诉他们  这是个猜想
It doesn't matter. Just tell them, it's a guess.
明白吗  蓖麻毒素
Okay? Ricin.
他们会明白你说的是什么
They'll know what you're talking about.
杰西  如果你还有什么没告诉我的
Jesse, if there's something you're not saying,
你一定得告诉我
you've got to tell me--
我得走  我得去见个人
Look, I gotta go. I gotta go see some one.
杰西  对不起
Jesse. Look, I'm sorry.
对不起  我得走了  告诉他们
I'm sorr-- I gotta go. Just tell them.
好吗  快  告诉他们
Okay? Now! Just do it!
你好  请让我进去好吗
Hello? Can you buzz me in, please?
让我进去
Buzz me in!
你想干嘛
What do you want?
咱们得谈谈
We need to talk.
你跟谁一起
Who's with you?
没别人  就我  让我进去
No one, just me. Let me in.
居然跑来这里  真不知道你怎么想的
I don't know what you're thinking coming here.
天啊
Oh, Christ.
现在还有关系么
What does it matter?
所有的  所有的一切都要结束了
Everything, it's all-- all coming to an end.
你到底知不知道发生了什么
Do you even know what's happening?
从头到尾发生了什么
the full scope of what's happening?
他们把我带去了沙漠
They took me out into the desert.
用布蒙住了我的头
They put a hood over my head
然后开车把我拉到沙漠
and drove me out into the desert,
要我跪下
on my knees.
他们用我的家人恐吓我
They threatened my family,
不光是汉克
and not just Hank.
还有我的妻子  我的孩子
My wife, my children...
现在只是时间早晚的问题
It's just a matter of time now.
我现在还能保护他们
I was-- I was able to protect them for now,
但是
but...
古斯会马上采取行动
Gus is going to make his move...
我  我不知道时间
and I don't-- I don't know when.
我不知道地点  也不知道方式
I don't know where or how.
我只知道马上就要开始了
All I know is it's going to happen.
而我无力阻挡
And I'm powerless to stop him.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
你干了什么
Why did you do it?
为什么
Why?
杰西  古斯逼得我别无选择
Jesse, Gus gave me no choice.
我不得不打电话给毒品管制局
I had to call the DEA
来保护我的家人
to protect my family.
我还能怎么做
What else could I do?
不  不  你个婊子养的
No. No, you son of a bitch.
你知道你做了什么
You know what you did.
冷静  冷静
Okay, look, just--
把枪放下
just put the gun down.
好吧  把枪放下  我们谈谈
Okay? Just put it down, and we'll talk.
行吗
All right?
你告诉我  告诉我  你认为我做了什么
You tell me-- tell me what it is you think I did.
布洛克  你为什么要给他下毒
Brock-- why did you poison him?
谁是布洛克
Who's Brock?
你昨晚在我客厅里见过他
You saw him in my living room just last night.
你走到我门前  直接就看到他了
You came to my door, and you looked right at him,
别跟我说你不认识他
so don't tell me you don't know him.
那个男孩
The boy.
杰西  我完全不知道那些人是谁
Jesse, I have no idea who these people are.
现在  拜托  好吧  是布洛克
Now, please-- Okay, that's Brock,
是他被下毒了吗
and-- and he was poisoned?
蓖麻毒素  他快死了
The ricin! He's dying
因为有人给了他蓖麻毒素
because someone gave it to him,
而你我二人
and only you and I
是这个世界上唯二
were the only two people on earth
知道这点的人
who knew about it.
等一下
Now wait a minute.
Wait a minute.
也许他去翻了你的口袋  然后
Maybe he went into your pockets and accid--
不
No!
我有
I had it.
今天早上我的口袋里还有蓖麻香烟
I had the cigarette with the ricin in my pack this morning.
我最后一次看见布洛克是在昨天晚上
The last time I saw Brock was last night,
今天早上  我把香烟换到了新口袋里
and this morning I switched the cigarette into a new pack.
布洛克根本没可能自己拿到
There's no way Brock took it himself.
杰西  你根本没想明白
Jesse, you're not thinking clearly.
听着  你自己说的
Listen, you said it yourself
你今天早上还有
that you had it this morning.
那我怎么可能拿到
Then when could I have possibly gotten it?
你  你让索尔做的
You-- You had Saul do it.
-什么  -对
- What? - Yeah.
对  我过去他的办公室
Yeah, I went to his office.
他打电话给我  说今天一定要见我
He called me and just had to see me today.
他那个大块头保镖搜遍了我全身
His big man-mountain bodyguard patted me down.
他肯定是那时候偷走的  对吗
That's when he must've stolen it off of me, right?
这就是你们的计划  是不是
That's the plan? Was that the plan?
杰西  为什么
Jesse, why?
为什么  看在上帝的份上
Why, in God's name,
我为什么要给一个孩子下毒
would I poison a child?
为了报复我
To get back at me.
因为我在帮古斯
Because I'm helping Gus,
这就是你报复的方式
and this is your way
你要在你死之前把我的心活活撕开
of ripping my heart out before you're dead and gone.
快承认
Just admit it.
承认你的罪行
Admit what you did.
快承认
Admit it!
我什么也没做
I did not do this!
闭嘴
Shut up!
别再撒谎
Stop lying!
我没  我没撒谎
I'm not-- I'm not lying.
我没撒谎  你听我说
I'm not lying. Just listen to me.
听我说  我有什么好处呢
Listen to me. What would I have to gain?
怎么可能  怎么可能会
What possible, possible could--
谁  谁会
Who-- who would--
上帝啊
Oh, my God.
嗨
Hey.
别笑了
Stop laughing.
Stop laughing!
我一直在等
I have been waiting.
我等了一整天
I have been waiting all day,
等着古斯
waiting for Gus to send
派他的某个手下来杀我
one of his men to kill me...
居然是你
and it's you.
你知道谁
Who do you know
谁对于利用孩子毫不愧心吗  杰西
who's okay with using children, Jesse?
你知道谁可以任由一个孩子被杀而无动于衷吗
Who do you know who has allowed children to be murdered?
是古斯
Hm? Gus!
他总是先发制人
He has-- He has been 10 steps ahead of me at every turn,
只有征得了你的同意
and now the one thing that he needed
他才能除掉我
to finally get rid of me is your consent,
现在他得逞了
and, boy, he's got that now.
你妥协了
He's got it.
而且他不仅得到了你的同意
And not only does he have that,
还操控你
but he manipulated you
成为了他的枪手
into pulling the trigger for him.
只有我们俩知道蓖麻毒素的事
Only you and I knew about the ricin!
才怪  你根本不相信
No! You don't even believe that
古斯的摄像头无处不在
Gus' cameras everywhere.
拜托  你听听自己的心声
Please. Listen to yourself.
他知道  他自始至终都无所不知
No, he has known everything all along.
你今天都去了哪里  实验室吗
Where were you today? In the lab?
难道你觉得不可能是
And you don't think it's possible
是泰鲁斯把你柜子里的香烟拿出来的吗
that Tyrus lifted the cigarette out of your locker?
别傻了
Come on.
你还看不出来吗
Don't you see?
你是最后一块拼图
You are the last piece of the puzzle.
你正是他所需要的一切
You are everything that he's wanted.
你现在成了他的毒师
You're his cook now.
你成了毒师  你还证明了
You're the cook, and you have proven
没有我  你也可以称得起一间实验室
that you can run a lab without me,
现在你这位毒师有理由杀我了
and now that cook has reason to kill me.
好好想想吧
Think about it!
计划太妙了
It's brilliant.
那你动手吧
So go ahead.
动手
Go ahead.
如果你认为我有能力做这件事  那就动手吧
If you think that I am capable of doing this, then go ahead.
把子弹射入我脑门
Put a bullet in my head
立马杀了我
and kill me right now.
动手
Do it!
Do it.
我会动手的
I'll do it.
动手
Do it.
你要去哪里
Where are you going?
我要去找那狗杂种
I'm going to find the son of a bitch,
然后毙了他
and I'm going to kill him.
不  别去
No, don't.
他会知道你过去的
He'll see you coming.
你靠近他前就死了
You'll die before you get anywhere near him.
我才不管
I don't care.
杰西  杰西  你只要上车
Jesse. Jesse, just get in your car.
开走就好
Just go.
Just drive.
不  怀特老师  不管怎样  我都会杀了他
No, I'm going to do this one way or another, Mr. White.
那让我帮你
Then let me help.
天呐  平克曼先生
Oh, Jesus, Mr. Pinkman,
我不想对你重复了
I'm not going to keep telling you.
除非征得家属允许
Unless the family wants you in there,
不然你不能进来
you're not allowed.
你不能总这样擅自进来
You can't keep coming in here like this.
听到了吗  听得懂吗
You hear me? You understand?
平克曼先生  我得叫保安了
Mr. Pinkman, I'm going to call security.
好了  来吧
All right, here we go.
快走吧
Come on now.
平克曼先生  我最后警告你一遍
Mr. Pinkman, final warning.
你现在该去干活了
You need to be at work now.
我告诉过你了  我不去
I already told you. I'm not going.
你这批货要作废了
You've got a batch that will be ruined
如果真作废了
and an employer who will be very upset
老板会不高兴的
if that happens.
你以为我会在乎吗
And I could give a shit.
我不走
I'm not leaving here.
如果我老板不满意
If my employer has a problem with that,
他可以自己跟我说
he can tell me himself,
而不是让他的小跟班来传话
not his errand boy.
给我...
Get--
我不认识这个人
Hey, I don't know this guy!
叫保安来
Call Security!
有人打我
I'm being attacked!
好  这就对了
Yeah, that's right.
这里有情况
We've got a situation.
他应该 注意到我了
他要跟你说话
He'd like to speak with you.
我告诉过你  我不走
I told you, I'm not leaving.
他就在楼下
He's downstairs.
泰鲁斯把情况都向我汇报了
Tyrus told me what's happening--
那个孩子的病情
the sick child.
我能理解你有急事
I understand your preoccupation,
可是  杰西  我有生意要做
but, Jesse, I am running a business.
我需要你回到实验室把活干完
I need you back at the lab to complete the cook.
你干完就能回来了
You can return when you're done.
不行
I can't.
你一定清楚  这样对我们双方都好
It is, as you must know, in both of our best interests.
楼上那个小男孩快死了
That little boy upstairs is dying.
我不能走  我也根本不想待在这里
I can't be away. I don't even want to be here now.
如果他有什么三长两短  我不能不在身边
I can't be away if something happens, if he--
我深感遗憾
I am very sorry.
我可以帮得上忙吗
Is there anything I can do?
我是这家医院的股东
I am on the board of this hospital.
我可以推荐医生给你
I can recommend doctors,
确保能满足他的一切所需
make sure he gets whatever he needs,
获得最好的治疗
the best treatment.
他没病
He's not sick.
他是被下毒了
He was poisoned.
怎么会
How did that happen?
那些医生
The doctors--
也不知道
they don't know.
这批货
This current batch...
现在一定是废了
is surely ruined now.
对吗
Correct?
陪着这个孩子
Stay with the boy.
泰鲁斯会销毁这批货  然后清理容器
Tyrus will dump what's there and clean the tanks.
你到时再做一批新的
You will start a new batch
等你下周准备好
when you are ready to return...
回归
next week.
来了
There you are.
继续走
Keep going.
为什么停步
Why'd you stop?
Why did you stop?
为什么停步
快  快
Come on. Come on.
Come on, come on.
拜托  天呐  拜托
Please. Oh, God, please.
拜托
Please.
不  不  不  别走
No, no, no. No, don't go.
别走  别走  别走
Don't go, don't go, don't go.
别  别啊
No. No.
他娘...
Oh, sh...
不要啊
No.